<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Vaibhavduggal &#8211; Vaibhav Duggal</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description>Digital Home</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 09:21:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>./../../../wp-content/uploads/2022/08/icons8-astronomy-64.png</url>
	<title>Vaibhavduggal &#8211; Vaibhav Duggal</title>
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Chapter 1</title>
		<link>./../../../2022/08/13/chapter-1/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2022/08/13/chapter-1/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Vaibhavduggal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 09:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=34</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hey Cody! Where are you? I&#8217;m in the bathroom mom. Ok, son. Have your breakfast sweetheart. &#160;Ok, mom. Mom after my breakfast I am going to my Grandpa’s house. Have a good day Cody. Oh yeah! He called me yesterday. He has to show me something and His house is<a class="moretag" href="./../../../2022/08/13/chapter-1/index.html"> Read more&#8230;</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hey Cody! Where are you? I&#8217;m in the bathroom mom. Ok, son. Have your breakfast sweetheart.</p>



<p>&nbsp;Ok, mom. Mom after my breakfast I am going to my Grandpa’s house. Have a good day Cody.</p>



<p>Oh yeah! He called me yesterday. He has to show me something and His house is as old as a ghost house which is an ancestral house (more than 100 yrs. old) His house was a palace too.</p>



<p>Hey, grandpa, I am here.</p>



<p>Oh, Cody! Nice to see you, I want to talk to you about something. Yes, Grandpa said, Cody. So, when I was cleaning my grandfather’s room I found a chest, but it needed a key.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td></td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td><strong>&nbsp;</strong></td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p>&nbsp;I tried to open it with my special locked door opening skill but it broke my pin, then when I was looking at it I saw a name on the chest ‘Mr. Horus Amathon Mack Anderson Renaldi’. After Hearing that name both me and Grandpa were surprised that it is our caste at the end, which means it is someone from our family! (And yes! My name is Cody Renaldi)</p>



<p>‘Grandpa you should be having our Family Book’ I said. Good Idea Cody! But what is your plan? My plan is that our Family book is having every biological information of each Family Member of ours which means we can find that name in this book. You are such a brilliant child Cody said, Grandpa.</p>



<p>But I haven’t seen it</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>2</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p>Since I was a kid. Neither do I grandpa said. ‘Oh, now I understand! I have solved my riddle!’ said Grandpa. What are you saying, Grandpa? My Grandfather gave me a Key when I was a kid and told me that this key was given by his Grandfather and he also told me that this will help him to remember him by unlocking the Secrets’ said, Grandpa. But I didn’t understand what he said and now I wear it to remember him. So Grandpa you are thinking that this key is the key to open this chest? Cody, now I will tell you my plan! So, as I have said&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;This key that I am wearing was given to my grandfather by his Grandfather and my Grandfather gave this to me, and that riddle means this will open our secret means this chest! said, Grandpa. You are as brilliant as I am Grandpa! I said. But Cody why somebody from our family didn’t open the chest? said, Grandpa. Yes, Grandpa, I was also thinking this only.1-hour later grandpa and I also exposed this truth and Believe me or not the chest is having a magic barrier and we confirmed this by putting the key into the chest when grandpa put the key in the chest and tried to open it then grandpa got a low voltage shock. So Grandpa what will we do now said, Cody.</p>



<p>I think only you can open it,</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>3</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p>Because when you touched the chest and tried to open it you didn’t get the shock but I got and by the way, the last member of our family special. What do you mean Grandpa? I said. Means that you can open the chest, and my father always told me that the last member of the family is special, and I was special but I didn’t know but now I am not special because I had children and then your father didn’t know that he was special and Then you were born and he lost the chance and now you are the last member and special too said, Grandpa.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td><strong>&nbsp;</strong></td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p>Now we are getting very close grandpa, said Cody. So Cody I hope you understood what I am saying ? said,Grandpa. Oh yes, Grandpa!. So as expected, I tried to open the box and surprisingly I opened it without a shock!. And after seeing inside the box we were shocked that our family book was inside the box with some extraordinary things. I picked up the book and again I was shocked by my mouth open, that there was my picture but no one has ever touched the book since I was born! Now we are getting heart attack after seeing the other material first, we found a blank map, a pocket edition book written with weird words, a wand just like Harry Potter’s magic wand, and also some other things like that. We just relaxed and start to read our family book, and searched for the name written on the chest and it was written on the front page! But after reading about him we were now a little serious. Because I was written “ Who is reading about me means you are very special, and you can now only save me!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2022/08/13/chapter-1/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
